ricebowl.my 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - RiceBowl.my

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RiceBowl collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [https://www.ricebowl.my](https://www.ricebowl.my/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by RiceBowl.

RiceBowl is not intended for children under 13 years of age.

Your Privacy Rights

RiceBowl collects information about you and uses this information to help you connect with employers and other job seekers and to provide other services to you. This policy describes how your information is collected and used and your choices with respect to your personal information.

Scope of this Policy

This policy applies to information we collect on sites and applications owned or controlled by RiceBowl or its affiliated companies (“RiceBowl”).

RiceBowl is not responsible for the data use practices of ad networks, other parties with whom we work with to provide you personalized services, or those who access your information on our sites or applications.

Information We Collect

We collect the personal information you choose to provide us. We also collect non-personal information about you, which includes demographic information and how you use and interact with RiceBowl. We may also acquire information about you from third parties to further personalize and enhance your experience.

How We Use Collected Information

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, respond to you, and operate and improve our sites and applications. Our services include showing you personalized content and advertising on RiceBowl or other sites with which we have a business relationship. We may use your information to contact you about RiceBowl updates, conduct surveys, or to provide informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

Information you share in public areas of RiceBowl may be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world. We strive to provide a safe, secure environment by attempting to limit access to our database to legitimate users, but we cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorized users store or transfer information you give to us, so you should not post sensitive information to RiceBowl.

How We Share Information

We share your information with third parties who help us deliver our products and services to you. These third parties may not use your information for any other purpose. With your consent, we may use your information to contact you about products or services available from our affiliates. With your consent, we may disclose your information to third parties who may contact you about their products or services. We also share information where legally required. We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of RiceBowl’s business units.

How We Store Your Information

We store your information to make your interaction with RiceBowl more efficient, practical, and relevant. You may review, update, or delete the personal information you share with us at any time by accessing your account. When you delete your personal information, we will retain logs and non-personal information about you along with an archival copy of your information, which is not accessible by you or third parties on the Internet. If your personal information was previously accessed by others using RiceBowl, we are unable to delete the information from their systems. You may turn off cookies. This will adversely affect your use of RiceBowl.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Changes to this privacy policy

RiceBowl has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

[RiceBowl

](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy)

08-06 Tower B,  
Vertical Business Suite,   
Avenue 3, Bangsar South City,  
No 8, Jalan Kerinchi 59200 Kuala Lumpur.  
+603 22423616 / +603 22423617
